// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "It is introduces the problem and gives the background information needed for the argument and thesis statement",
      answer: "Introduction",
      options: [
        "Introduction",
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Reason",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "The of the essay contains the reasons. It is a three or more paragraphs that explain the reasons why you support your thesis",
      answer: "Body",
      options: [
        "Introduction",
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Reason",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "The __ are included in the introduction",
      answer: "Reason",
      options: [
        "Introduction",
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Reason",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "Refers to the written, spoken and visual forms of language that people live with every day",
      answer: "Text",
      options: [
        "Text",
        "Discussion Text",
        "Factual Text",
        "Persuasive Text",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: "It informs, instruct or persuades the reader by giving fact or information",
      answer: "Discussion Text",
      options: [
        "Text",
        "Discussion Text",
        "Factual Text",
        "Persuasive Text",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
      question: "Are pieces of writing that tell a story or entertain",
      answer: "Literary Text",
      options: [
        "Literary Text",
        "Characteristic of letirary",
        "Persuasive Text/Writing",
        "Discussion Text",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
      question: "Offers the opportunity to convince the reader/listener to adopt a particular viewpoint or to believe in what the writer is telling",
      answer: "Persuasive Text/Writing",
      options: [
        "Literary Text",
        "Characteristic of letirary",
        "Persuasive Text/Writing",
        "Discussion Text",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
      question: "Also know as argumentative text/content present an issue sorrounding a particular topic",
      answer: "Discussion Text",
      options: [
        "Literary Text",
        "Characteristic of letirary",
        "Persuasive Text/Writing",
        "Discussion Text",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
      question: "Are those that ask you to answer whether or not something true",
      answer: "Question of Fact",
      options: [
        "Question of Fact",
        "Questions",
        "Questions of Value",
        "Question of Policy",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "Ask the writer to explain what they would do",
      answer: "Question of Policy",
      options: [
        "Question of Fact",
        "Questions",
        "Questions of Value",
        "Question of Policy",
    ]
  },

  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];